{
  "decks": [
    {
      "name": "React Router",
      "description": "React Router is a collection of navigational components that compose declaratively with your application.",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "hi",
      "description": "bye",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "name": "sdvsd",
      "description": "dsvsdv",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "name": "ijknjk",
      "description": "opkpo",
      "id": 5
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "What path will match the follow Route?\n<Route>\n  <NotFound />\n</Route>",
      "back": "All paths. A route with no path matches all URL's",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "front": "What does <Switch> do?",
      "back": "Renders the first matching child <Route> ",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "front": "fgtmjtfgcm",
      "back": "gfmgfmfgm",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "front": "hehehe",
      "back": "hahaha",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "front": "egegesg",
      "back": "tyuertre",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "front": "rehreh",
      "back": "rhegerg",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "front": "iujonhbukij",
      "back": "jhvjkl",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "front": "ihbiyhv",
      "back": "jhvjkl",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "front": "ytcdjyf",
      "back": "ulyfguloi",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "front": "as",
      "back": "as",
      "deckId": 5,
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "front": "as",
      "back": "asdfsfds",
      "deckId": 5,
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "front": "dgdfsg",
      "back": "sdfsdf",
      "deckId": 5,
      "id": 15
    }
  ]
}